{"Topic": "Fairs and Festivals", "Subject": "General Knowledge", "Data": [{"Question": "In which State is the religious festival Ganesh Chaturthi celebrated with gusto?", "op1": "Rajasthan", "op2": "Gujarat", "op3": "Maharashtra", "op4": "Madhya Pradesh"}, {"Question": "Which festival occurs at a different time from the other three?", "op1": "Sankranti", "op2": "Ugadi", "op3": "Lohri", "op4": "Pongal", "Answer": 3}, {"Question": "Which of the following combinations of the States and the festivals mainly celebrated there is not correct?", "op1": "Rajasthan - Gangaur", "op2": "Gujarat - Durga Puja", "op3": "Maharashtra - Ganesh Chaturthi", "op4": "Uttar Pradesh - Krishna Janmashtami", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "Flamingo Festival is organised in which State?", "op1": "Telangana", "op2": "Karnataka", "op3": "Nagaland", "op4": "Andhra Pradesh", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "The Desert Festival, an annual event in Rajasthan that displays local folk arts and culture, aerobatics, camel races, is held at", "op1": "Jodhpur", "op2": "Jaisalmer", "op3": "Barmer", "op4": "Bikaner", "Answer": 4}, {"Question": "Ahatguri in Assam is famous for \u2013", "op1": "Bullock-cart racing", "op2": "Cock fighting", "op3": "Bull taming", "op4": "Buffalo fighting", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "Which city hosts the Kala Ghoda Art festival in February every year?", "op1": "Mumbai", "op2": "Jaipur", "op3": "Kolkata", "op4": "Bengaluru", "Answer": 4}, {"Question": "Kambala is a traditional buffalo race held in the State of", "op1": "Karnataka", "op2": "Tamil Nadu", "op3": "Telangana", "op4": "Kerala", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "Festival of Holi falls on \u2013", "op1": "New Moon Day", "op2": "Full Moon Day", "op3": "One day before Full Moon", "op4": "One day after New Moon", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "Sarhul is a festival celebrated in \u2013", "op1": "Rajasthan", "op2": "Maharashtra", "op3": "Uttarakhand", "op4": "Jharkhand", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "Which State hosts the annual Surajkund crafts fair?", "op1": "Haryana", "op2": "Himachal Pradesh", "op3": "Uttar Pradesh", "op4": "Rajasthan", "Answer": 4}, {"Question": "Where is Pushkar Fair held?", "op1": "Jodhpur", "op2": "Ajmer", "op3": "Jaipur", "op4": "Udaipur", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "Atla Taddi is a festival of which State?", "op1": "Karnataka", "op2": "Maharashtra", "op3": "Jharkhand", "op4": "Andhra Pradesh", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "Losoong festival is celebrated in which of the following states?", "op1": "Tibet", "op2": "Arunachal Pradesh", "op3": "Sikkim", "op4": "Kerala", "Answer": 4}, {"Question": "In which of the following states is the Hornbill Festival held annually?", "op1": "Mizoram", "op2": "Assam", "op3": "Sikkim", "op4": "Nagaland", "Answer": 3}, {"Question": "Sonepur, the venue of one of the largest cattle fairs is located in which of the following states?", "op1": "Gujarat", "op2": "Rajasthan", "op3": "Bihar", "op4": "Uttarakhand", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "With which of the following festivals is Jallikattu associated?", "op1": "Onam", "op2": "Pongal", "op3": "Vishu", "op4": "Shivarathri", "Answer": 3}, {"Question": "Chapchar Kut is a festival of which State?", "op1": "Manipur", "op2": "Nagaland", "op3": "Mizoram", "op4": "Meghalaya", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "Which city is famous for Bali Jatra festival?", "op1": "Cuttack", "op2": "Ranchi", "op3": "Raipur", "op4": "Patna", "Answer": 3}, {"Question": "Which one of the following festivals is not celebrated almost simultaneously in the month of January each year?", "op1": "Makar Sankranti", "op2": "Pongal", "op3": "Gudi Padwa", "op4": "Lohri", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "In which country is the Salzburg Festival held every year?", "op1": "Germany", "op2": "Austria", "op3": "Switzerland", "op4": "France", "Answer": 4}, {"Question": "Jallikattu is bull taming event held mainly in \u2013", "op1": "Telangana", "op2": "Goa", "op3": "Karnataka", "op4": "Tamil Nadu", "Answer": 3}, {"Question": "In which State is the Madhavpur Mela held annually?", "op1": "Rajasthan", "op2": "Haryana", "op3": "Gujarat", "op4": "Chhattisgarh", "Answer": 1}]}